<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<sect1 id="release-6-6-1">
    <title>Release notes for version 6.6.1</title>

    <para>
        6.6.1 is a bugfix release over 6.6. Most library APIs have not
        changed, so code that worked with 6.6 should continue to work
        with 6.6.1.
    </para>
    
    <para>
        Many, many bugs have been fixed relative to 6.6. Far too many
        to list here.
    </para>

    <para>
        The other changes in this release are:
    </para>

    <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
            <para>
                GHC works on Windows Vista.
            </para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
            <para>
                GHC can now be used to compile C++ files.
            </para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
            <para>
                There is an
                <option>--install-signal-handlers=&lt;yes|no&gt;</option>
                RTS flag. The main use is to stop GHC installing signal
                handlers when you are putting your code in a DLL.
            </para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
            <para>
                Newtypes can now be defined using GADT syntax.
            </para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
            <para>
                Linear implicit parameters are no longer accepted.
            </para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
            <para>
                There is a manpage for <command>ghc</command> and
                <command>ghci</command>.
            </para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
            <para>
                The building guide has been moved to
                <ulink url="http://hackage.haskell.org/trac/ghc/wiki/Building">the wiki</ulink>.
            </para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
            <para>
                GHC now comes with the <literal>filepath</literal> library.
            </para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
            <para>
                The <literal>base</literal>
                package has various bug fixes, as well as a couple
                of interface changes that shouldn't affect most users.
                The version number has been bumped from 2.0/2.1 to 2.1.1.
            </para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
            <para>
                The <literal>Cabal</literal> package has had various bug
                fixes. The version number has been bumped from 1.1.6 to
                1.1.6.2.
            </para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
            <para>
                The <literal>Win32</literal> package has various bug fixes.
                The version number has been bumped from 2.0/2.1 to 2.1.1.
            </para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
            <para>
                The <literal>regex-base</literal> package has a couple of
                bug fixes. The version number has been bumped from 0.71
                to 0.72.
            </para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
            <para>
                The pretty-printer in the
                <literal>template-haskell</literal> package has been
                improved. The version number has been bumped from 2.0 to 2.1.
            </para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
            <para>
                The <literal>unix</literal> package has various bug fixes.
                The version number has been bumped from 1.0/2.0 to 2.1.
            </para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
            <para>
                There are newer versions of all of the extralibs.
            </para>
        </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
</sect1>

